I want to start off with just a simple
question. How many of you actually post
organic content? Okay, pretty much every
single one in this room. How many of you
have signed clients with organic
content?
How many of you make 100K per month with
organic content?
Okay, just three of them. [laughter]
400.
Okay, just just two now. [laughter]
So my goal today with this presentation
and this talk is to actually show you
what our 400k a month organic flywheel
system actually looks like so that you
can actually take it and implement it
for yourself. And I was in a lot of you
guys' position just a year ago. I was
posting content but nothing actually
really hit. And I basically made it my
mission to crack organic because this
was the biggest lever that I can pull to
create the biggest advantage in my
industry. And what ended up happening
was I raised my prices from $5,000 to
$45,000. I went from 5k followers to
$122,000 followers. And I went from
5,000 subscribers to 27.8 subscribers
all in a span of 2 years.
My total cash went from 51,000 cash
collected to over $48,000 cash with an
85% close rate and 93% show rate. And so
I'm going to cover the three biggest
changes that I actually implemented that
you can implement this as well. And
number one, I'm going to go over how you
can actually lower your audience's
guard, how you can find your unique
mechanism, and how you can actually
treat your brand like a media company.
Okay, so the first one is lowering your
guard. How many of you sell a service?
Every single one of you. The problem is
that everyone is focused on creating
content to get clients. And that's when
they actually never build a brand. When
you think about the biggest people in
the space, the best personal brands
don't actually feel like they're selling
anything. And when you look at Hermos's
rise to the top,
the the line that he used all the time
was, I have nothing to sell you. And he
said that for years and years and years,
and he built that amount of goodwill.
Now, what does that fundamentally do
when someone feels like there's nothing
to benefit from you?
It lowers your guard, right? It lowers
your guard and you're able to be
influenced. And then when he decided to
go and pitch something, he was able to
make a $100 million in a single day
because of all that pent up goodwill
and he had a bunch of upsells and he
made so much money in that single event
in that in that webinar and now he's
actively selling the workshops and
everything. Right now, when you watch
these brands, it feels like they aren't
selling. And so what this fundamentally
does is it lowers your guard and it
allows you to become easily influenced,
which makes the entire process so much
easier. When I look at your guys's
content, the first thing I think about
is like, what does this guy want from
me? Because you're giving so much value.
You're giving so much information. Like,
what does this guy actually want from
me? And it brings my guard up. Have you
guys ever walked in a store and
immediately the salesperson is going up
to you and asking, "What do you want?"
In that position, what ends up happening
is you don't feel at ease because you
can't browse and shop around and you
can't like you don't really want to buy
anything anymore because you feel the
pressure. And so what you guys are doing
with your content is you're making your
prospects feel pressured. That's what's
making you fight an uphill battle when
you're posting content.
Content is about lowering your viewers
guard. And the best way you can do this
is by postexit positioning. I say this
all the time. If you look at the biggest
personal brands, every single one of us
takes this positioning of I don't need
your money because I've already created
a vehicle that have made me a ton of
money. If you think about a Hermoszi,
the perception that he creates is that
he runs his private equity, a portfolio
of companies that make him tens if not
hundreds of millions of dollars every
single year. But what you guys don't see
is that he also makes so much damn money
by selling consulting and workshops.
There's a reason why he's actively
promoting that. If you look at a guy
like let's say William Brown, he's taken
the approach of I've exited my company
that the trading company that that that
he that he ran up and then now he's
making more money with his actual B2B
consulting business. So they're taking
the postexit positioning to allow you to
lower your guard down so that you feel
like they have nothing to benefit from
you which in turn allows everything to
be so much easier so that you can
actually trust them. The first part is
actually understanding this fundamental
concept. Doing this will make sure that
you don't fight an uphill battle and
just make everything so much easier.
Okay. And so how do we build a strong
personal brand that actually drives
sales effortlessly? It's through
YouTube.
Your focus when you're scaling your
business and scaling your brand should
be 80% on YouTube and 20% on Instagram.
Okay? And I I see the a huge discrepancy
between the clients that come from
Instagram, the clients that come from
YouTube. On Instagram, we get a lot of
these split pays of people, you know,
paying half up front, whatever the case
may be. But every time I get an inbound
booking from YouTube, it's usually a
$45,000 pay in full. And the reason why
is because the sophistication level of
someone that is on YouTube is so much
higher compared to Instagram. If
someone's on Instagram and they find
your page, the problem is that they're
scrolling and Instagram that Instagram
algorithm pushes your account. But when
it's on YouTube, YouTube displays 20
different videos and they intentionally
click on your title and your thumbnail.
So everything about what they're doing
is intentional and it allows you to
spend more time with them as well. My 28
my 28,000 subscribers contribute to 80%
of my sales. And if you look at your
best performing clients, every single
one of them were pre-sold on you, most
likely because they've consumed some
type of long form content.
They were pre-sold and bought them
before they even hopped on a call with
you. And that's the key when you build
your content engine around YouTube.
Everything trickles down because if you
have a competent back-end process, which
I will go over, everything can be
clipped up. And 70% of my Instagram
videos are actually completely clipped
up and completely handled by my
post-production team. Meaning, I don't
script them. I don't film them. These
are existing videos that I've already
filmed for YouTube. They're repurposed
on Instagram. Instagram gets their
attention and YouTube converts them and
gets them sold on you. Okay? So, your
audience needs to spend the maximum time
with you, which means you need to
actually provide as much value as you
can on YouTube to make sure that these
guys are getting as much as they can out
of you before they actually even touch
your pipeline.
Number two is finding a unique
mechanism. Once you understand the
postexit positioning, you need to
understand that building a brand comes
down to these four stages. The first
stage is being admirable. Second stage
is being likable. Third stage is being
credible. And the fourth stage is being
trustable. And here's the part that most
people get wrong. They try to skip
straight to being credible. And they
post content. They lead with value. They
give information. They tell people why
what they're doing right now is wrong.
And they wonder why it falls flat. It
falls flat because everyone on social
media is posting content telling people
what to do. And so if everyone is doing
that, you are positioning yourself as
every other person on on on Instagram
and YouTube.
And so when did you last spend a
significant amount of money with someone
that you didn't like? Probably never.
Probably never.
Nobody does, right? Trust is built in
sequences. And too many of you are
trying to skip the trust building
process and trying to tell someone what
to do before they even like you or
before they even give a about what
you have to say. So stage one is being
admirable. This is the first stage. If
you get low views, this is the first
stage that you got to master and that
you got to really understand. The first
thing you have to realize is that nobody
you have to realize that nobody cares
about you. Literally nobody.
There's 200 million creator accounts on
Instagram and 4.5 billion reels shared
daily, every single day. Before doing
anything, you have to give your audience
a reason to care about you, right? And
so I want you guys to ask yourself, this
is the perfect reflection question. What
are the three reasons that you can give
your audience to admire you? You just
need to come up with three. But the key
thing here is that when you combine all
three, only you should be able to have
that positioning. So for me, mine's the
fact that I make 400k a month at 20.
That's one very, very strong reason.
Another strong reason is that I'm
balancing this with being a full-time
university student. That's another
strong reason. And then the last thing
is I value my family and
non-materialistic items over everything
in the industry where everyone is
showing their cars, their watches, and
everything. All this materialistic
stuff. I don't do that. And so when I
combine these three things here, I don't
know a single other person that has
these three. Maybe they have one or
maybe they have two, but they don't have
all three.
These are your three unique mechanisms
that your entire brand is built upon.
And that's what makes you different
compared to every single person in your
industry. It's not about the value that
you give. It's not about the
information. It's not about what you do.
It's about the context that you give
your audience.
Every single big personal brand has
context that they've given their
audience that has allowed them to
position themselves completely separate
from every other person. And if you're
not getting views, that means your
unique mechanisms when tied together are
simply not good enough. So you need to
either do one of do two things. You need
to actually reverse engineer what makes
you different or you just need to do
more cool so that people actually
give a
And so your pro your question is most
likely how do I find my unique
mechanism? You need to ask yourself what
makes you different and stand out
because every single person in this room
is making above 30k a month.
You need to ask your clients why they
chose you over the hundreds of other
competitors that sell the exact same
solution. And what I call this is I want
you guys to implement the buyer mirror.
Every client should fill out a buyer
mirror form during the entire onboarding
process. Now let's go through each
question. The first one is where did you
first come across me? Whether it was
Instagram, YouTube, referral, podcast,
what was it? And the second question is,
what was the first piece of content or
moment that made you take me seriously?
These this is the top ofunnel content
that I always go back towards to get my
ICP's attention. Instead of guessing
what to post or thinking or using
claude, just use your client data.
Because if you want more of who you're
already signing, you can just ask them.
I say this all the time, the best
content strategist is not, you know,
what you see that goes viral. It's
literally by asking your clients because
they paid you. You just want more of
them, right? So, the second question
gives you the ideas that you can do as
top ofunnel content. The third question
is, what was the last piece of content
that you watched that push you to book a
call?
This is your middle ofunnel content.
Your middleunnel content is what
actually creates trust with your buyer
to take that next step forward and book
in a call and actually pay you cash. You
need to understand what actually peaks
their attention and what peaks
their buying process. And when you have
these two, top of funnel and middle
funnel don't become this guessing game.
It becomes extremely intentional.
There's some other ones like what is the
main reason you decided to reach out
when you did. Right before our call, how
convinced were you that you sign up?
What were your biggest hesitations
before joining? There are other coaches
who help with content and branding. Why
did you choose me? Why me? Was it my
morals? Was it my values? What was it?
You need to figure this out for your own
clients. All right. So, if you're
watching this video, you're probably
trying to sign clients with content.
[music] And if you're posting content
right now, but it's just not resonating
with your audience. This is for you. I
want to give you our exact buyer mirror
form that we get every single one of our
clients to fill out when they on [music]
board with us. This form tells us
directly why they chose us, what makes
us different, and what we could have
done better in our content to attract
them earlier. This is the exact insight
that you need to intentionally apply
into your content so that [music] you
can sign more content, scale, and
actually scale your business. We've
gotten over a 100 responses and that is
the single reason why the brand is as
[music] intentional as it is today. It's
because we got direct insight from the
people that paid us so that we can make
our content better. If you want the
exact form that we personally use,
[music] go ahead and click the link down
below, access it for free. Now, back to
the video. Now, once we have that, we
understand what makes us admirable.
Now, we got to we got to make ourselves
likable so that people can actually
trust us and want to listen to us.
Again, just because someone makes a lot
of money doesn't mean you want to listen
to him. If he makes a lot of money, but
he shares the same morals and values as
you, now you want to listen to him.
Okay? So, if people don't like you on
some level, they won't stay long enough
to be influenced by anything else you
do. Because every single one of you, you
may be doing well, you know, 100K, 500K,
a mill, but there's always going to be a
person out there that makes more than
you. And so if you're only competing
based on being admirable, there's no
point. There's always a bigger shark.
Likability doesn't mean being overly
positive or charismatic. It just means
showing what makes you different.
And it means your audience view is
someone they'd actually want to spend
time with outside of your service.
So look at the answers that you've
implemented from your buyer mirror form
that your clients have filled out. These
are some examples that I have for
myself. So this is one of the questions
and someone said one of my clients said
some coaches may have one or two things
going for them but not the whole
package. You seem like the only one who
checked all the boxes smart ridiculous
proof your morals and values both as a
person and as a leader in your space. I
like how you prioritize storytelling,
serving and being authentic and mindset
work. And I appreciate that you
prioritize fulfillment and treating your
people like family.
And there's this other person that said,
"The biggest thing I was drawn to was
the focus of becoming an industry
leader. You also seem more genuine. You
care about your clients. You're down to
earth. You're not materialistic. I have
no interest in just building a business
to maximize revenue. I want to help the
people around me."
That's how you go from posting generic
content that only gets a hundred if not
thousands of views to creating specific
content where you share real experiences
and when people watch your content, they
feel connected to you. They feel
personal.
And so I took this from a viral format
that this guy used and he basically
broke down what he spent his money on.
This his paycheck, right? He got a what
does it say here? $212,000 paycheck. And
he basically showed the lifestyle that
he's living, the cars that he has, the
apartment rent, um the holidays, like
everything, right? Just living the life,
like the typical things that we would
spend on or that we see people spend on.
I took that idea and I had a complete
spin-off on it. So, I talked about my
paycheck, but I talked about how little
I spent on shopping, how the fact that I
had no car lease payments, the fact that
all my money is going to index funds, my
investments or back to family or just
convenience, right? And so I took that
the comments went from being invest more
into your education and you know
everyone being a financial adviser in
his video to people looking at my video
and being like wow that's I've never
seen this before. This is different. I
really appreciate you sharing this
insight. And so I'm attracting the
people that aren't too materialistic
about every about life and that actually
want to invest in their future in a more
sophisticated ICP. But how did I find
that? Remember the answer that I got
from the last question
was being authentic and not not being
materialistic. So if I showed that more
in my content, do you see how would I
attract that same person?
Is everything making sense so far?
>> Okay, perfect.
Now we get to be incredible. This is the
part that you guys are all experts in,
right? And only once someone's only once
someone likes you and relates to you,
then they are ready to hear about your
results. Then they are ready to be told
what to do. And so this is where you can
share your client results. This is where
you can share your personal results.
This is where you can give value to your
clients. But too many of you don't have
the admiraability stage and likability
stage and are skipping to this and
wonder why it falls flat. Why do we
listen to the industry leaders in our
space? is because we have context that
they've gone through so much that
we don't want to go through that we feel
like we can get their lessons without
the pain and the struggle that they went
through. That's fundamentally what
content is. You have to appeal to your
audience's selfish desire to watch your
content. And so this is you giving
value. Now, I want to be very clear when
I say this because I see a lot of people
posting value and even if they do all
three steps right, they may they still
may not ever make it work.
Giving value isn't regurgitated
information that can be found on 10
other channels. It's not.
This is information that you have that
shows why you're different. And so when
you say some type of value content or
when you're filming a video, you got to
ask yourself, am I the only one that can
actually say this out loud? And are
other people that have posted content
already saying the same thing?
Because cred credibility tells people
that you can get them where they want to
go. But if your content is generic and
basic and none of the value is actually
sticking, it's useless. Everything you
did was useless. Okay? And so the best
quote unquote value videos that I've
done have performed well always after I
bought a new program or mentorship. And
so my philosophy behind value is I take
what's behind pay walls and I'm the
first to put it out in the free content
world. Now what does this do? This
forces people to watch my content
because they can't find it anywhere
else. Think about how I started this
entire presentation.
I didn't leverage just my 400k a month
with complete organic. I leverage people
that every single one of you know to
make my point, you know, stronger. And
there's not a single person in the
audience right now that that's on their
phone except Jeremy. [laughter]
[gasps] But you get the idea. Like
there's not a single person because I'm
able to give so much credibility
that I'm forcing you to listen. I'm not
just leveraging my results, but I'm
leveraging the people around me. And so
you feel like you're getting lessons and
insights from investing $200,000 by just
listening to me. That is the perception.
It's all about packaging. It it's it
rarely is about the value and the
expertise that you actually share. It's
the positioning in which you do it. And
if I sat here and said that, oh, I just
post organic content from my clients,
but I didn't invest any money. I didn't
mention how much I spent. I didn't
mention the names that I learned from.
It wouldn't be as interesting.
Now, we get to stage four. This is being
trustable. Okay? Trust is built over
time. It's the accumulation of every
single piece of content that you made,
every promise you've kept, and every
time you showed up and delivered real
value. If your if you don't get inbound
leads every single month saying that
they're ready to pay you in full, that
means that your content is working
against you. There is no neutral ground
in content. When you post content,
either clients when when prospects watch
that content, they either feel a huge
urge to want to pay you or they move
away from you because your content is
And the biggest the easiest way to
test this is seeing that if you get DMs
of people wanting to pay in full,
the single best way to fast track
building trust is by showing instead of
telling. Okay. Now, we basically
pioneered a format where I I I looked at
client interviews and you know, client
interviews are the best ways to sign
clients. This is by far the most
important sales asset. But the problem
is that client interviews are selfish.
it it's all about your service. It's all
about the client. It's there's nothing
about the viewer. And so I wanted to
figure out how to actually make a client
interview interesting. And so what I did
was I created this format right here.
This is a video that I did of a client.
And the packaging of this video looks
like a like a value front facing video
that you click on, right?
And so in this video, what all I did was
instead of sitting down and asking
regular questions like a client
interview that is boring that no no one
really wants to watch, I walked Wyatt
walked me through every single decision
that he made in order to go from 7K a
month to making 312K cash collection in
90 days.
So now he's able to give value while
breaking down how we helped him. So when
people watch this video, they still get
value even if they decide to join or not
to join because why it's breaking down
this process.
I did this with Emma as well and we
broke down her entire decision-m process
from A to Z on how she went from 30K a
month to 125K a month in a span of 90
days. But you get the idea. The value
itself is there, but it's all about the
packaging and the way that the audience
perceives it. If you can make your
bottom ofunnel content appeal to a wider
demographic instead of just people that
are interested in your service, that's
when special happens. And when I
posted this video, I've had a just over
$120,000 directly attributed to this
format right here.
This is, in my opinion, the future of
client interviews because client
interviews are getting too boring.
They're too outdated. This is the future
of it. Okay? And I've broken down
everything into an SOP. Um, I was
planning to send it to you guys on
Instagram, but my Instagram is banned.
So, I'll just send it on WhatsApp. This
is a 11-page document SOP on exactly how
you guys can implement this because I'm
assuming that every single one of you
has amazing testimonials and amazing
client results and you're doing your
audience a disservice by not showing
them. So, this is the perfect way to
show them instead of telling them that
you're good.
And when someone trusts you, they don't
need a sales call, right? They DM you
and say, "Hey, I have the money. Like,
just send me the link." And we've had a
lot of people paying into DMs because of
this, but it's only because we've built
trust in sequences and we never skipped
any steps.
The goal of our brand is to build trust
at scale. And the best advice I can give
you guys is treating your brand like an
actual media company. Okay?
Most of you post like a creator.
you're the one person that's doing
ideation, scripting, filming, editing,
posting, and you know, that's not a
brand. That that's not that's not a
personal brand. That's not a business.
It's it's you're the bottleneck. And so
the one who the ones who win treat
content that like they're running a
media company.
The creator waits for ideas to come to
them, whereas a media company has a
system that produces proven ideas and
generates predictable results. Instead
of asking, "What should I post?" I just
want you guys to start building a
machine that answers that for you. Okay?
And so everything we do runs on two
pipelines. And I'm going to break both
down. The first one is the
pre-production, what we do before we
film the video. And the second one is
the post-production, what we do after we
film the video. Okay. Stage one,
pre-production.
We've essentially built out an AI agent
that scans everything we've already
published and pinpoints what's word
before. And what this allows us to do is
it doubles allows us to double down on
everything from the hooks, formats, and
angles so we can generate predictable
results.
The objections you hear on your sales
calls every single day are also content
gold. An objection that you get on a
sales call is something that is stopping
hundreds if not thousands of people from
working with you. And you discover that
on a sales call. So if you're hearing
the same objection over and over again,
think about how many people in the
thousands if not tens of thousands have
the same idea, have the same thought
process. And so the goal with content is
we want to single and pinpoint every
single doubt, obstacle or objection that
is stopping someone from buying.
And so the way I look at content is like
every day that I'm producing middle of
funnel or bottom of funnel content, I am
creating content to solve these
objections so that I never hear them
again. That is what I look at.
And so we also take direct favor from
our clients to understand why they
bought into us so we know what concept
to double down on. And so I need you to
get in the constant habit of asking your
clients what do they want to see in your
videos.
A lot of people just overkill complicate
content for what it is. They think it's
this rocket science. And it's not hard.
You just have to be intentional about
everything that you're doing. And so
once we've come up with a content idea,
we put it through this system. It gets
scored and validated answering two
questions. Is the addressable market big
enough? And can I package this to pull a
wide demographic in?
Most creators throw content at a wall
and hope it sticks. But we're
intentional from the moment the idea is
generated up until we press post. Okay?
And then once an idea has been approved,
our editor and our AI agent handles the
rest. We do competitor research based on
what videos have already performed well
in the past. They generate a package and
thumbnail. Obviously, the editors
helping out with this process and then
we do data collection and script as
well. Okay. And so all that I need to do
is film.
By the time we film, the idea has been
sourced. It's scored with our internal
algorithm. It's reviewed by AI. It's
researched. It's packaged in the way
that I want it. And so I know all of
this so that when I'm speaking in my
content, I know exactly how I'm going to
do it. I know the title and the
thumbnail of this video as I'm
presenting this video, presenting right
now before I even stepped up on stage.
That's the level of intentionality that
you have to have. And so, we're not
gambling on camera. We're simply
executing a proven concept backed by
data.
This is the last part that I want to go
through, okay? Post-production. And then
I'll we'll get to a Q&A.
We've invested over like $50,000 into
optimizing our content systems for
scale. And this is the exact system that
allows us to convert one, you know, over
50 hours of footage into 60 short forms
and six long form videos every single
month. It starts with how you structure
your team. And so if you just have an
editor and you're telling him to clip up
your your videos with no intention, with
no SOPs, with no training,
that's that's the reason why you're
stuck, right? And so we used to face
this exact bottleneck. And that's why
we've designed the team built for scale.
This is what my team looks like. I have
a CMO who's my head of content and he
manages this entire system. I have a
head editor in long form that is leading
the long form charge. He's he's making
sure that everyone is executing what he
needs to do. I have a thumbnail designer
under that where his entire goal is to
just do thumbnails and research what's
working and be creative. And then I have
a junior editor that manages the second
account and make sure that everything is
clipped up. Now the key thing is that my
head editor actually has leverage. He is
not clipping these videos from scratch.
The junior editor is actually clipping
up the boring parts of a video, the
parts that you know are not going to
make the final cut. And then the head
editor is adding the animations, adding
the entire, you know, the making the
packaging look amazing. And then on the
shortfront side is the same thing. I
have a head editor that makes that holds
everyone under him accountable. And I
have one dedicated clipper that goes
through all of my content, my hours and
footage, my hours of footage, and finds
the best value that I give
so that we can clip it up. And then my
junior editor edits the first revisions,
sends it back to the head editor. And
it's this entire process and this entire
flywheel. We've removed the guesswork
from our entire post-p production
process because of the people I have in
place. The moment a video is uploaded,
clipped, and assigned, the editing team
knows exactly how to execute. If you're
wondering why you're not consistent,
there's one of two things. Either you
have no SOPs or no training, or you're
not spending enough money. How
many of you sign clients with ads? Just
a raise of hands. Every single one of
you, how much do you guys spend on ads?
Just shout it out real quick. Per month.
10K. How How much did you say? Okay.
70k. Anyone else? 10K.
I spend 15K a month on my content team
and I generated a 24x return on
investment every single month. If you
look at organic content the same way you
guys look at ads, you're going to take
it seriously. And so I was a business
owner that hated this You know, I
didn't want to do it. It was
unpredictable. But when I forced myself
to actually spend money, that's when I
got intentional about it. When I hired a
competent person, that's when I got
intentional.
And so the same way that you give a
about your rorowaz on ads because you're
spending, you have to do the same thing
for organic. If not, it's not going to
work. You have to spend an uncomfortable
amount of money so that you actually
give a because this is the mo this
is the biggest long-term competitive
advantage that you could ever create.
People can copy your ads. People can
copy your sales process. They can copy
your fulfillment, but they can't copy
your brand because that's built over
years of work.
So every format that we've done follows
a documented SOP based on proven winners
that my head of content creates. If
we're doing some type of live
transformation, we have an entire SOP
that that we give the editor so that
editors are not editing
based on competence or based on what
they think. They're editing based on
what we want.
Every single format that I've posted,
there's an specific editing criteria
that I've engineered for that so that
none of it is up to luck.
We collect data on viewer spikes in our
long form content to find the best clips
with the most viral potential to be
converted into short form. If you post
on YouTube, you can actually see the
retention graph. And if you see right
here, this is a perfect spike. We posted
this and it got 60,000 views. And so
it's intention behind the clipping
process from the YouTube videos to make
this process entire super super easy.
Not only that, but the full transcript
of our long form content goes in the
cloud and it's running our clipping SOP.
We basically select the clips that used
to take hours and now that happens at
scale in a span of minutes. Okay,
the most important part of the
production process actually happens
after the video is posted. And so every
week we review what performed and feed
the outliers back into Claude, which
becomes an ideation machine. And when
you tie claude with the buyer mirror
that you're getting and the feedback
that you're getting from your clients,
can you see how content is predictable
now? It's easy. And so every winner
becomes an input for the next round of
ideas. And it's this entire loop when
you get content that actually performs
well. The winners feed the ideation
process. The ideation feeds the
production. The production feeds the
performance. And then the performance
feeds the ideation again. And it's this
entire loop. And so when you post a
piece of content, you need to be hyper
analyzing the entire process that goes
behind it because too many of you treat
content as if it's just something on
your to-do list that you just got to get
done. Every single one of you knows that
content is important. But because of
your lack of intentionality with the way
you set up the systems, that's why
you're stuck. But if you have these
systems that scale, that's what's going
to get you out of the process of trying
content, not not seeing it perform, and
then going back to ads and then starting
from zero again. Okay. The creators who
burn out are doing everything
themselves, and the brands that compound
are the ones who build the systems to
operate at scale.
Perfect.
>> [applause]